<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/collections/all.atom"/>
  <title>Free Healthy Hobbies</title>
  <updated>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Free Healthy Hobbies</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628163690573</id>
    <published>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/thinner-leaner-stronger-the-simple-science-of-building-the-ultimate-female-body"/>
    <title>Thinner Leaner Stronger: The Simple Science of Building the Ultimate Female Body</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Free Healthy Hobbies</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0277/9001/6589/products/w_4416b231-4cf6-4ace-89fe-1d8e708f0e8b.png?v=1589223228"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Free Healthy Hobbies<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            14.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>This book has helped thousands of women build their best bodies ever. Will YOU be next?</h2>
<br><span>If you want to get lean, defined, and strong as quickly as possible </span><b>without crash dieting, good genetics, or wasting ridiculous amounts of time</b><span> in the gym . . . </span><u>regardless of your age</u><span> . . . you want to read this book.</span><br><br><span>Here's the deal:</span><br><br>
<h2>Losing fat and building lean muscle isn't as complicated as the fitness industry wants you to believe.<span> </span><u>This book is the shortcut.</u>
</h2>
<br>
<li>
<b>You don't need to:</b><span> </span>Spend hundreds of dollars per month on the worthless supplements, "detoxes," or "skinny teas." Most pills and powders do<span> </span><u>absolutely nothing.</u>
</li>
<br>
<li>
<b>You don't need to:</b><span> </span>Constantly change up your workout routine to get lean, defined muscles. It's<span> </span><u>much simpler</u><span> </span>than that.</li>
<br>
<li>
<b>You don't need to:</b><span> </span>Waste a couple of hours in the gym every day grinding out grueling workouts. In fact, this is a great way to get<span> </span><u>nowhere.</u>
</li>
<br>
<li>
<b>You don't need to:</b><span> </span>Slog away at boring cardio to shed ugly belly, hip, and thigh fat. In fact, you probably don't have to do<span> </span><u>any cardio</u><span> </span>to get the body you really want.</li>
<br>
<li>
<b>You don't need to:</b><span> </span>Obsess over "clean eating" and avoiding "unhealthy" foods to get fit. Instead, you can get the body you want<span> </span><u>eating the foods you love.</u>
</li>
<br><span>Those are just a few of the harmful lies and myths that keep gals from ever achieving the lean, toned, sexy, and healthy bodies they </span><u>truly desire.</u><br><br><span>And in this book you're going to learn something </span><b>most women will never know</b><span> . . .</span><br><br>
<h2>The exact formula of exercise and eating that makes losing 10 to 15 pounds of fat while building lean, sexy muscle a breeze . . .<span> </span><u>and it only takes 8 to 12 weeks.</u>
</h2>
<br><span>Here are just a few of the things you're going to discover in this book:</span><br><br>
<li>The<span> </span><b>10 biggest fat loss and muscle-building myths and mistakes</b><span> </span>that keep women overweight, weak, and frustrated.</li>
<br>
<li>The 3 scientific laws of lean muscle growth and fat loss that literally<span> </span><b>force your body to get fitter, leaner, and stronger.</b><span> </span>You'll be shocked at how easy it really is to build lean muscle and lose fat once you know what you're doing.</li>
<br>
<li>How to create flexible diet plans that help you<span> </span><b>transform your body composition eating the foods you love</b><span> </span>. . . and without ever feeling starved, deprived, or like you're "on a diet."</li>
<br>
<li>A paint-by-numbers training system that will help you<span> </span><b>add lean muscle to all the right places and get sexy, athletic curves</b><span> </span>. . . spending no more than three to six hours in the gym every week . . . doing challenging, fun workouts you enjoy.</li>
<br>
<li>A no-BS guide to supplements that will show you what works and what doesn't,<span> </span><b>saving you hundreds if not thousands of dollars each year</b>.</li>
<br>
<li>And a whole lot more!</li>
<br><span>Imagine . . . </span><b>just 12 weeks from now</b><span> . . . being constantly complimented on how great you look and asked how the heck you're doing it . . .</span><br><br><span>Imagine enjoying the added benefits of </span><b>high energy levels, no aches and pains, better spirits</b><span>, and knowing that you're getting </span><b>healthier every day</b><span> . . .</span><br><br>
<h2>The bottom line is you CAN get that<span> </span><u>"Hollywood babe" body</u><span> </span>without following boring, bland "bodybuilder" diets or living in the gym. This book shows you how.</h2>
<br><b>SPECIAL BONUS FOR READERS!</b><br><br><span>With this women's fitness book, you'll also get a </span><b>FREE 56-page reference guide</b><span> with all of the book's key takeaways, a year's worth of </span><i>Thinner Leaner Stronger</i><span> workouts, 10 premade meal plans for cutting and lean bulking, and more!</span><br></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628163690573</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">14.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628161298509</id>
    <published>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/roar-how-to-match-your-food-and-fitness-to-your-unique-female-physiology"/>
    <title>ROAR: How to Match Your Food and Fitness to Your Unique Female Physiology</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Free Healthy Hobbies</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0277/9001/6589/products/w_c076dace-fb9d-4a9a-b709-760bac9a3129.png?v=1589223167"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Free Healthy Hobbies<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            19.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><span>Women are not small men. Stop eating and training like one.</span><br><br><span>Because most nutrition products and training plans are designed for men, it’s no wonder that so many female athletes struggle to reach their full potential. </span><i>ROAR</i><span> is a comprehensive, physiology-based nutrition and training guide specifically designed for active women. This book teaches you everything you need to know to adapt your nutrition, hydration, and training to your unique physiology so you can work with, rather than against, your female physiology. Exercise physiologist and nutrition scientist Stacy T. Sims, PhD, shows you how to be your own biohacker to achieve optimum athletic performance.</span><br><br><span>Complete with goal-specific meal plans and nutrient-packed recipes to optimize body composition, </span><i>ROAR<span> </span></i><span>contains personalized nutrition advice for all stages of training and recovery. Customizable meal plans and strengthening exercises come together in a comprehensive plan to build a rock-solid fitness foundation as you build lean muscle where you need it most, strengthen bone, and boost power and endurance. Because women’s physiology changes over time, entire chapters are devoted to staying strong and active through pregnancy and menopause. No matter what your sport is—running, cycling, field sports, triathlons—this book will empower you with the nutrition and fitness knowledge you need to be in the healthiest, fittest, strongest shape of your life.</span></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628161298509</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">19.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628159103053</id>
    <published>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-11T14:46:45-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/the-fitness-mindset-eat-for-energy-train-for-tension-manage-your-mindset-reap-the-results"/>
    <title>The Fitness Mindset: Eat for Energy, Train for Tension, Manage Your Mindset, Reap the Results</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Free Healthy Hobbies</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0277/9001/6589/products/w.png?v=1589223115"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Free Healthy Hobbies<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            16.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>How would it feel to have the body you've always wanted, a huge boost in energy, and the mindset to keep it forever?</p>
<p>Have you ever felt frustrated about not getting the results you want? Do you feel you are eating the right foods and doing the correct workouts but your body still isn't changing as quickly as you want? Are you grinding through your workday with low energy levels, praying for the next day off so you can sleep in?  </p>
<p>If this sounds familiar, then<span> </span><i>The Fitness Mindset</i><span> </span>is for you.<span> </span><i>The Fitness Mindset</i><span> </span>gives you everything you need to get the body you've always dreamed of, ramp your energy levels through the roof, and develop the mindset to keep it forever. When you listen to this audiobook and implement Brian's proven strategies, you will:</p>
<p> <br></p>
<ul>
<li>Know exactly what foods work best for you and how to eat to increase energy, lose fat, and build lean muscle</li>
<li>Learn how to combine tension-style workouts and High Intensity Interval Training (Hiit) to build the body you've always wanted</li>
<li>Build better habits and find your 'why' so you never lose motivation again</li>
<li>Develop strategies to minimize stress, anxiety and the fear of rebounding so you can create a bulletproof body and mind</li>
<li>Finally get into the best physical and mental shape of your life</li>
</ul></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://free-healthy-hobbies.myshopify.com/products/4628159103053</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="USD">16.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
